flipanim.com 2017-12-02

# FlipAnim - create flipbook animations online!

Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  * We will collect and use personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain additional consent for other uses of the information from of the individual concerned or as required by law.
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up to date.
  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
  * We will make information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information readily available to site visitors.
  * We will use 'cookies' and 'local storage' to store information required to properly operate FlipAnim site. Addidtionaly third party libraries like Google Adsense and Google Analytics can use 'cookies' and 'local storage' to work properly. You can disable storing data in your browsers privacy properties, but we not guearantee that FlipAnim will be working properly after disabling it.

We are committed to conducting our site in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. Please contact us if you detect any unauthorized access to your or others account or data on FlipAnim website.
